photos-public-domain.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Photos Public Domain

### Privacy Policy

Posted in: 

Photos-Public-Domain.com respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains our treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on this site. This Privacy Policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices. We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. 

**What Information Does  Photos-Public-Domian.com collect?**  
Photos-Public-Domain.com does not collect any personal information from any user. Our web servers automatically record the IP address and referring URL from each visitor.

**Does Photos-Public-Domain.com use cookies?**  
Photos-Public-Domain.com does not employ the use of cookies however, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We have contracted with Google AdSense to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ad networks may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertising Network. 

For More information on the information collected and used by Google AdSense including how to opt out of cookies, please see Google’s Privacy Policy at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>

For More information on the information collected and used by Conversant Media  please see Conversant’s Privacy Policy at: [https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)

**How will you use, or potentially use, this information?**  
Photos-Public-Domain.com uses information collected by our servers for the sole purpose of performing anonymous statistical analysis of our web visitors. 

**What options do users have to easily limit the use of their personal information?**  
Photos-Public-Domain.com does not collect any personal information from any user, so we do not have an Unsubscribe function on our website.

**Who should I contact if I have any questions about your Privacy Policy or anything else related to your website?**  
You may contact us anytime by using our [secure contact form](http:// "http://www.photos-public-domain.com/contact-us/"), and one of our dedicated staff members will respond to you as soon as possible (usually within 24 hours).
